<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="eula_is_agreed_key">end_user_license_agreement_is_agreed</string>
	<string name="eula_title">License agreement</string>
	<string name="eula_agree">Agree</string>
	<string name="eula_disagree">Disagree</string>

	<!-- Developer's infomation -->
	<string name="eula_developer_name">IoriAYANE</string><!-- assigned to %2$s -->
	<string name="eula_cout">the Nagoya District Court</string><!-- assigned to %3$s -->

<!--  http://www.developer-resource.com/sample-eula.htm -->
<string name="eula_message">
END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR %1$s IMPORTANT PLEASE READ THE TERMS 
AND CONDITIONS OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE CONTINUING WITH THIS PROGRAM INSTALL:
 %2$s\'s End-User License Agreement (\"EULA\") is a legal agreement between you
 (either an individual or a single entity) and %2$s.
 for the %2$s software product(s) identified above which may include associated
 software components, media, printed materials, and \"online\" or electronic documentation (\"SOFTWARE PRODUCT\").
 By installing, copying, or otherwise using the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA.
 This license agreement represents the entire agreement concerning the program between you and
 %2$s, (referred to as \"licenser\"), and it supersedes any prior proposal, 
 representation, or understanding between the parties. 
 If you do not agree to the terms of this EULA, do not install or use the SOFTWARE PRODUCT.\n
\n
The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties,
 as well as other intellectual property laws and treaties. The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is licensed, not sold.
\n
\n
/// GOVERNING LAW\n
This EULA is governed by the Japanese laws.
I and User each irrevocably and unconditionally submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of %3$s,
 and each knowingly waives any objection that the courts therein do not have personal jurisdiction or
 that the courts are an improper forum, or not a convenient forum.
</string>
	
</resources>
